https://destinationbeauty.com/privacy-policy/

Toggle navigation
NavigationHomeAbout Plastic Surgery Centers ThailandOur SurgeonsOur Team and ServicesResources Plastic Surgery Gastric SleeveProcedures Breast AugmentationTummy TuckLiposuctionBreast LiftFaceliftNose JobFull Body LiftBreast ReductionEyelid SurgeryDental ThailandGastric SleeveDeals & PackagesFree EvaluationTestimonials Client StoriesPlastic Surgery Thailand VideosBefore and AftersPricelist Plastic Surgery PricelistPayment Plan AustraliaPayment Plan New ZealandFlyback CoverContact usWhat information do we collect?We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form or Send us an email.When registering on our site, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:; To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs); To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you); To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs); To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested. ; To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature; To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. You can at any time request us to stop contacting you and for us to delete your details, simply email: info@destinationbeauty.com with your request.How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.Do we use cookies?Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain informationWe use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.Do we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties, such as our partner hospitals, our partner travel agent and our partner payment plan provider, who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.California Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceBecause we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act ComplianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.Online Privacy Policy OnlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.Disclaimer:Hygeia Healthcare / Destination Beauty helps you find medical treatment opportunities abroad. The role of Hygeia Healthcare is to act as a marketing agent for medical facilities and arrange medical treatment packages with the option to include a holiday package. The agreement to have surgery is strictly between the patient and the hospital. The final decision about whether the patient is a candidate for the chosen procedure(s) will be made by the surgeon during the pre-surgery evaluation. Hygeia Healthcare does not offer any medical advice and is in no way liable for the actions of third parties, such as partner hospitals, travel agents and payment plan providers. You are aware of and acknowledge the role of Hygeia Healthcare as described. You further accept that the decision to have medical treatment abroad is your decision and that you are aware of any risks involved.Your ConsentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Our service of providing appointments at hospitals for clients is covered by the below disclaimer: Changes to our Privacy PolicyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.This policy was last modified on 31st January 2012Contacting UsIf there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.www.destinationbeauty.comDestination Beauty by Hygeia Healthcare Co. Ltd. 39 Somerset Park Suanplu, M Floor, Soi Suanplu, Tungmahamek, Sathorn, Bangkok 10120 Thailand info@destinationbeauty.com +66 26775650Email: info@destinationbeauty.com TH : (+66) 2 105 4046 AU: (+61) 2 8417 2428 NZ: (+64) 9801 0396Privacy PolicyDisclaimerYour Free Evaluation
×
